## Samantha Brown

## Technical Project Management

Miami. FL (754) - 302 - 7148

samantha24.sb@gmail.com

LinkedIn

Technical project manager, who's efficient with data extraction and presentation which deliver business value from common data sources like Google Doc, Slides, and Sheets. I have seven years of customer service experience that helps me utilize logic and empathy when choosing the appropriate systems to be used for a project. My interest in providing security in all possible forms will aid in not only delivering the best result as planned but leading the team during the project life cycle.

## Skills

- Budget Management, Time Management, Stakeholder Management, Risk Management, Project Documentation
- Predictive Methodologies, Agile Methodologies, Team Collaboration, Group Facilitation, Mediation
- System Development Life Cycle, Multitasking, Data modeling and evaluation

## **Projects**

### Sierra 2.0

- Presented the framework for a three-six month website update with a five-year maintenance period
- Utilized the agile values as the foundation of each slide to reinforce the building of the teams' culture
- Tech used: time management, agile framework, and Google Slides

## **Experience**

Thinkful Remote Studied Technical Project Management December 2020

- Practical mastery of Google Slides, Sheets, Docs, and research for creating necessary project
- Create multiple diagrams to demonstrate the project life cycle and the Systems Development Lifecycle
- Conduct a mock performance review and an interview
- Learn industry best practices for frameworks, methodologies, and interpersonal skills on various levels
- Gain knowledge for facilitating "meetings" and soft skills for managing various personalities

#### Securitas Florida City, FL Security Guard September 2020 - Present

- Interact with a wide range of people and permit entry to the store once guidelines were met
- Enforce store, state, and federal safety procedures and COVID-19 policies
- Maintain the organization's stability and reputation by complying with legal requirements
- Complete reports by recording observations, information, occurrences, and surveillance activities; interviewing witnesses

### **Brosnan Security**

Key Biscayne, FL December 2019 - September 2020

Security Guard

- Utilized an 8 condo digital repository to check whether the visitor needed to be verified prior to providing
- Print parking pass once the visitors' access to the property has been authorized or add visitors into the system first

Alorica Cutler Bay, FL August 2013 - December 2019

# **Escalation Specialist**

- Processed twenty-plus escalated cases daily
- Trained and managed agents for the Pre-AP program to assist administrators
- Handled supervisor request and communicated with clients about unsolved escalated cases

## Education

### **Cleavans Protection Services**

State Security License

Miami. FL December 2018